Hardware called up, so this folder mainly consists of the code of hardware abstraction layer and the
supporting modules procured good for the hardware.
It consists of the hull or audio video, USB, DV, camera and so on.
The Hull modules are consumed by the Somizi's layer to discover and operate corresponding devices available
on the device.
For example, the camera service will be using the camera module to discover and operate corresponding
camera devices available on the device.
So under the hardware folder, we can find all the Hull related modules here.
The Google folder is specific to Google devices, where you can find the holes for the Pixel and the
Google Camera.
Similarly, if you go to the Interfaces folder, you can see all the halls related to different devices
off the mobile or any other hardware which is supported by Android.
For example, if you take the camera.
So this package consists of the Hull modules required to communicate with the camera hardware within
the form.
So, for example, the camera service will be making use of these camera modules to communicate with
the camera devices are available in their mobile form.
Similarly, you can find the hall for audio here, and here is the automotive one.
So this basically communicates with the sensors in an automotive AR or any automotive vehicle which
you make use of Android.
And similarly, here you can find for all the hardware components.
So this one is for the power and the radio to the power manager will be making its own power service
will be making use of this hub to get the battery power off the mobile phone, for example, and similarly
to communicate with the radio.
And here you can find the DB tuner hands and so on, and there are many other folders here which are
specific to different hardware or different OEMs.
So here you can see the Samsung Broadcom.
OK, so next folder is kernel.
The kernel folder contains the kernel corn flakes and some reboots, so please make a note that it doesn't
contains the actual Linux kernel.
Instead, it is basically for holding some of the kernel conflicts and reboots under the kernel and
find the conflicts folder and prebuilt folder and some tests.
So under config, you can see find the conference for different versions.
Floating are as you be similarly pre-built and find different versions of the kernel here.
And then there is a desktop folder which contains some of the tests.
Now we have the Lib Core Lib Core consist of many core libraries later today to own example bars for
Apache Team Harmony, etc. Under the Lib Core, we can find many library modules like, for example,
some again, find some point here and Jason is here and these are something let some tests related to
harmony back to harmony like native helper.
So the lib native helper consist of the dynamic library.
This is the basis of DNA library.
It consists of helper functions to use with Java native interface, so you can find the Lib Native help
out here, and it consists of DOM modules later to the journey.
Next, we have the out folder, so the folder is not the default folder with the A.P., so you'll find
out folder only after you build areas.
So after the build is complete, the code output is in this directory.
You can find the generated image folder built here.
So in my case, I have built RSP once so I can see all the output over here.
So here you can see find all the intermediate files plus the images.
And finally, we have the Packages folder, so the packages folder consist of the application package,
just like the stock Android apps, providers, AMS and many more.
So under the packages folder, there is a folder called apps that are apps.
You can find all the stock apps coming by default with AOSP.
For example, if you need to see all the automotive related apps, you can go straight here and here
you can see.
You can find all the stock apps like, for example, the dialer, media, app, radio, etc. And similarly,
these are the stock apps.
It comes as part of the mobile device, so the Launcher three is the launcher for the mobile phones.